Come on friends, let's go to the Ola Experience
Center and see completely, to what extent has the
scooter's gas started reducing, whether it has reduced or
not, bastard sir, I do
n't know for how many days I have kept it, let's see till when
and let's see completely, let's go there
[Prashansa] I am
waiting for the auto, the auto has not come yet,
finally an auto is visible in front,
it is coming, let's see if we should stop it or
not, the auto stopped, so
friends
[Sangeet] we went
there to show it, it will be done
after that
[Prashansa] it has
not reduced completely,
friends, the gas did not reduce at all there,
after that they started saying that they will do it before 15th August,
after that they will talk, if they will
not be able to do it, they will
delete it completely and show it to you guys